LAN PHUONG

MARKETING INTERN

0859992803

- phuongdl2803@gmail.com
- Hanoi, Vietnam

EDUCATION

Bachelor of International Communication 2023 - now

Diplomatic Academy of Vietnam

High school 2021 - 2023 Nguyen Tat Thanh Lower and Upper

Secondary school



EXPERIENCE

Academic and teaching assistant

2024 - now

Point Avenue

- Good understanding on the structure of a company in a academic field
- Good understanding on English programs
- Fluent English

Leader of Content Department High school English club

2021-2023

- Creating content/content series for Facebook page
- Deep research about event/PR
- Working with school administrations/teachers

Content creator on daily content

2022

Instagram

- Creating contents
- Instagram administration
- · Promoting contents
- SEO

Selling Moon cake for charity Highschool

2022

Planning marketing strategy

- Planning visual aid of the cake/packaging/...
- Researching on best sources of cake

CERTIFICATION

- IETLS 7.0 (certification attached with the CV)
- MOS Word
- MOS Excel
- MOS Powerpoint

ABOUT ME

I am a freshman studying international communication, specialized in marketing. I have desire with marketing field, I also want to be an marketer after graduation and willing to work with companies with all my passion and dedication. Therefore, a real experience coming in the first year is a one-of-a-kind opporunity for me to make my dream come true

SKILLS

- Organizational skills
- Creativity
- Interpersonal communication
- Flexibility
- Teamwork
- Plan management Communication planning
- Content creation (events, pages, websites,...)
- Office technology competence
- Teamwork

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Chinese (Basics)
- Korean (Basics)